Hello hello friends, I
welcome you to my channel Kumar Bilar, so
friends how are you, I hope you all are doing
well, so friends if we are going to talk about what
documents will be required if we are submitting our documents to the fort, then friends let's
start the video, so before starting the video
I would like to request you
that if you are new to my channel then please
subscribe to my channel,
like the video, comment and definitely save it, so
friends as I told you
that now you are buying a car, so get your car
insured and get it insured, you have bought a
new car, so if such
digging is being done on the car, an accident happens,
anything happens, the official thing is getting
damaged, then let us tell you
what are the things that are installed in the fort
and we will tell you which words have to be
filled and up to
how much amount you have to pay, so
friends first of all let
us talk, so comment  If
we talk by commenting, then first of all, the first thing that will be required for
you and the deal is that is, a
driving license, if
you do not have a driver's license, then you will
not be able to get your car, first of all, it is
very important for you to have a license and along with the
driving license, your PAN card
and your Aadhar card will also be required, PAN card Aadhar card
and that is, the main
Voter ID card is not required here,
if someone can ask for a Voter ID card, then it is
necessary to have a Voter ID card as well, so so many things
like, for those who apply for a claim after the first, so much
thing is very
important for that, that the numbers of Adil are needed, there it is
written, there it is a
digit, so we talk about it,
like the reference that you are using for
my car, up
to what percentage is it, so
friends, let us tell you that the
insurance of my car is up to full hundred
percent, that is, if there is any scratch on my car, then
we do not have to pay even ₹1,
we only have to pay the processing charge,
any, that  Is this the rule everywhere
that the pool insurance of the vehicle is
100 percent of cancer and safety, then you will have to
pay only the processing charge for your vehicle, apart from that
you will not have to pay anything, so friends, let us
tell you that you will not have to pay even ₹1 in the fort,
if the insurance of your vehicle is up to
100 percent, then if it is
90% then you will have to pay 10 percent, so
friends, your flame will be
lemon juice, that insurance,
you will have to pay Jio 4G according to the percentage of insurance you have done,
and well, let me
tell you that the vehicle of the fort will become
old, after that pollution
also develops, you will have to give the same
documents, what documents will you have to give,
PAN card, Aadhar
card, Voter ID card and pollution of the dip and
pollution and your driving
license, you will have to give these many things here, it will
go to the program and after going to the fort the vehicle will become yours,
then  You will be called from the agency,
so you can reset your vehicle near the depot, so
friends, it means the
day, in how many days you will
get the vehicle, so your entry will tell you
in how many days
you can receive all your things, that is, from here, so now the
agency people here will tell, so
friends, that's all for today, I
hope you have understood which ones are required
and what
is the insurance, how much
percentage will you have to pay on getting it done,
and so it is on the insurance, so
friends, that's all for today, so let's meet again, I would
like to request you that if you are new to my channel, then
subscribe to my channel, if you like the video, then please
like, comment and
share, so friends, that's all
for today, then we will
meet you in the next topic and in the next video,
if you need any information for blood lipids, then
you can comment and the
video is with you, my full effort to surprise